<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!DOCTYPE html>
<html>
<head>
<title>Plus UI v3.0.0</title>
<b:skin><![CDATA[ 
-----------------------------------------------
Blogger Template Style
Name:        Plus UI
Licence:     Premium Version
Version:     3.0.0
Author:      UI Plus
Author Url:  https://ui-plus.blogspot.com/

Premium Blogger Templates, Free premium blogger themes, Premium blogger templates free, Premium Blogger templates free download, SEO friendly Blogger Templates, How to download premium Blogger template for free?

--------{ About Plus UI }--------

Plus UI is Professional, Flexible & Highly Optimized Blogger Template. Best Blogger Template for Tech News, Marketing, SEO Tips, Videos, Food Sites and More. Plus UI has been optimized for major search engines so you can get the best organic results. It is also completely friendly to all mobile devices.
Plus UI blogger template is a modern template, which will provide you amazing and useful features. If ads are your main source of monetization, Plus UI is undoubtedly your best choice, as it has numerous flexible and customizable sections to add your ads.

--------{ Features of Plus UI }--------

• Google Translator, that will help visitors to read the articles in their own language.
• Table Of Contents
• Full Dark Mode support
• RTL Support
• Minified CSS
• Stylish and Responsive About Page
• Stylish and Responsive Contact Form
• Stylish and Responsive Sitemap Page
• Fully Responsive - The template size is flexible to fit every screen and the layout is neatly arranged by maximizing CSS performance.
• Optimized for ads - Ready-to-use Adsense ad slots have been provided in locations with high click rates
• Easy Customization - It's very easy to change the color, width to font through Blogger Theme Designer including widget settings in the Layout menu.
• Fully Optimised for Core Web Vital.

> Introducing Plus UI Add-ons in v2.6
• Following Add-ons (Plugins) are available in Plus UI v2.6
  1. Anti Ad-Blocker
  2. No Internet Connection Notification
  3. Cookie Consent Notice
  4. Bookmark Posts
  5. Categorised Posts
  6. Theme Color
  7. Music Player
  ....more....

--------{ Note }--------

• You must not distribute/resell the template.
• If you do so, your license kry will no longer work and will not get the updates.

--------{ Services }--------

• 1 Month Support for any issues, note that custom modifications are not included.

--------{ Contacting Us }--------

If you want to contact us regarding anything about this template, feel free to contact us through:





----------------------------------------------- 
*/]]></b:skin>
</head>
<body>
<b:section id='plusui'/>
</body>
 </html> 